<resources>
    <string name="app_name">delihome</string>
    <string name="GothamBook">fonts/Gotham.ttf</string>
    <string name="GothamRndBold">fonts/GothamRnd-Bold.ttf</string>
    <string name="GothamRndMedium">fonts/GothamRnd-Medium.ttf</string>
    <string name="GothamRndItalic">fonts/GothamRnd-MedIta.ttf</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_splash">ActivitySplash</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_pemesan_detail">ActivityPemesanDetail</string>
    <string name="api_key">AIzaSyC4RetJFb8ux8wtEwRMqpP6aNKPexgbH2w</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string-array name="nav_drawer_labels">
        <item>Menu</item>
        <item>History</item>
        <item>Discover</item>
        <item>Promo</item>
        <item>Help</item>
        <item>Customer Service</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="AnsFaq1">
        <![CDATA[
        Pesanan Pre-order akan dikirim pada tanggal pengiriman yang sudah ditentukan oleh vendor.
        <br>Pengiriman akan dilakukan pada jam 11 hingga jam 2 siang.
        <br>Pesanan Speed delivery akan dikirim dalam waktu kurang lebih 30 menit sejak pemesanan dilakukan.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq2">
        <![CDATA[
        1. Order : Hanya dengan memilih makanan yang anda inginkan di tabs speed delivery maupun Pre-order.
        <br>2. Checkout : Masukan alamat tempat lokasi anda dan nomor handphone.
        <br>Pastikan nomor yang anda berikan selalu aktif untuk memudahkan kami menghubungi anda mengenai order anda.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq3">
        <![CDATA[
        Pesanan yang telah diterima tidak bisa dibatalkan atau diganti dengan orderan yang lain.
        <br>Untuk penggantian alamat pengiriman dapat langsung menghubungi driver dengan jangka waktu paling lambat jam 9 pagi di hari pengiriman.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq4">
        <![CDATA[
        Pesanan Speed delivery akan dikirim dalam waktu kurang lebih 30 menit sejak pemesanan dilakukan.
        <p>
        <br>Pesanan Pre-order akan dikirim pada tanggal pengiriman yang sudah ditentukan oleh vendor.
        <br>Pengiriman akan dilakukan pada jam 11 hingga jam 2 siang.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq5">
        <![CDATA[
        Biaya pengiriman Speed delivery sebesar Rp 20.000,-
        <br>Biaya pengiriman Pre-order sebesar Rp 10.000,-
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq6">
        <![CDATA[
        Pembayaran Pre Order dilakukan menggunakan system Transfer. Pesanan akan dibuat setelah pembayaran dilakukan.
        <br>Pembayaran Speed Delivery dilakukan dengan system Cash on Delivery. Uang yang dibayarkan diharapkan sesuai dengan jumlah total.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq7">
        <![CDATA[
        Masaku adalah platform online pertama di Surabaya yang menyediakan makanan rumahan. Pengguna dapat memilih banyak varian makanan rumahan yang siap diantarkan hingga ke rumah.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq8">
        <![CDATA[
        Bila anda ingin mengecek semua menu di Masaku, buka aplikasi kami dan pilih tab <b>"speed delivery"</b> atau <b>"pre-order"</b> menu akan ditampilkan sesuai dengan kategorinya
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq9">
        <![CDATA[
        Jam buka untuk Speed delivery adalah setiap hari pukul 11.00-14.00
        <br>Jam buka untuk Pre-order ditentukan oleh masing-masing vendor.
        <br>Jam buka vendor akan dituliskan pada profile vendor. Standarnya dari jam 11:00 – 23:00.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq10">
        <![CDATA[
        Masaku tidak memiliki kuasa dalam hal ini. Order anda dapat ditolak oleh vendor bila
        kuota vendor yang tidak memadai, area anda tidak dapat dijangkau oleh vendor, maupun alasan-alasan lain.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="AnsFaq11">
        <![CDATA[
        Bila sudah memiliki account Masaku. Silahkan kembali ke halaman login dan klik lupa password. Password yang baru akan dikirimkan
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="contentCopyright">
        <![CDATA[
         All text and images on Masaku website or Masaku Mobile Application remains copyright of Masaku. Usage of any of this material is prohibited, unless authorised by the copyright holder. Masaku is authorised to use all images that are used on Masaku website and Mobile Application
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="contentTerms">
        <![CDATA[
          <p>By making a purchase with us on this website/Mobile Application, you are agreeing to the following terms and conditions.</p>
          <br/>
          <p>Prices</p>
          <p>All of our prices are exclusive of taxes.</p>
          <p>On the occasion that any item is incorrectly priced, we reserve the right to cancel the purchase and relist the product at the correct price.</p>
          <br/>
          <p>Privacy</p>
          <p>We only store necessary information required to make a purchase.</p>
          <p>We do not sell or lease any of your personal information. All information left with www.masaku.id or Masaku mobile application is entirely confidential.</p>
          ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="contentGuarantee">
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Masaku Mobile Application is committed to ensuring your food will be delivered to you. If the food you order are not delivered, we will refund your order.</p>
          ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="contentPrivacy">
        <![CDATA[
          <p>This is for reasons of fraud protection. Fraudulent orders will be submitted to the appropriate authorities.</p>
          <p>Masaku collects personally identifiable information that you may voluntarily provide on online forms, which may include: user registration, contact requests, guest comments, online surveys, and other online activities. The personally identifiable information (Personal Information) collected on this application can include some or all of the following: your name, address, telephone number, email addresses, demographic information, and any other information you may voluntarily provide.
In addition to the personal information identified above, our web servers automatically identify computers by their IP addresses. Company may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. To emphasize, IP addresses are not linked to personal information.</p>
          ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="contentDisclaimer">
        <![CDATA[
          <p>It is your own responsibility to ensure that you are fully aware of all of these terms and conditions when making a purchase on Masaku Mobile Application.</p>
          <p>Masaku reserve the right to change / modify these terms & conditions at their own discretion anytime.</p>
          <p>The images shown are only indicative in nature and the actual product may vary in size, colour etc.</p>
          <p>Masaku reserves the right to change any part or piece of information on Masaku Mobile Application without any notice to customers or visitors.</p>
          ]]>
    </string>
    </resources>